I'm already a cripple.
Since you won't give me a swift end,
will you at least answer me one question?
Can my eyes still be healed?
He once told me
that he could heal my eyes.
Let me glimpse this colorful world.
I want to know if he was lying to me.
I wasn't lying to you.
Wu Ming.
We finally meet.
Truly one in a million.
No wonder
my A Yi
for your sake,
would throw away her life.
This is
the Yin-Yang Dual Formation.
A welcome gift, prepared just for you.
The two forms beget the four phenomena,
and the four phenomena bury life and death.
One yin,
one yang,
one lives,
one dies.
Ling'er.
I forgot to tell you,
you
can only choose one to save.
Wu Ming, stay back!
Wu Ming.
Don't worry about me, Wu Ming!
Get out of here, quickly!
Brother.
Brother, save me!
Brother!
Save Ling'er!
Save me, Brother!
Save me!
Save Ling'er!
Wu Ming.
I'm already a cripple.
Save the one you ought to save.
Save me!
Save Ling'er!
Brother!
I'm begging you.
Save Ling'er first, Brother!
Brother!
Brother, save me!
Though we've known each other only briefly,
I know you have a compassionate heart.
So I've severed my own heart meridian,
cutting off any path to life.
Save me!
This is my own choice.
Brother!
You needn't blame yourself.
Save Ling'er!
I thought I had no lingering attachments to this world,
but I so longed to see you, just once.
Save me, Brother!
Whoever he saves,
he must abandon the other.
A thorn will be planted in his Dao heart.
What a vicious scheme.
Brother!
I'm begging you!
Save me!
You're finally here for Ling'er.
Brother, don't abandon Ling'er!
Save me first!
Brother!
Don't worry about me.
Save me first!
Go save Ling'er!
Brother!
Save me!
Save Ling'er!
Don't leave Ling'er behind!
Brother!
Huizi
Master
This...
Brother Ming
Why'd you bring an assassin back?
You killed Gui Chen?
Huizi
Activate the array, seal the clinic.
Don't let anyone in.
Yes.
Wu Ming
What can I do?
I'll write a prescription now.
You go prepare the medicine.
Okay.
Her heart meridian is severed.
How can she possibly be saved?
Seems you don't know what Wu Ming's capable of.
If he says he can save her, he can.
Impossible.
He's not some immortal.
Can he snatch souls from the King of Hell?
Anyway,
I don't believe it.
Then let's just
wait and see.
No matter how smitten you are with him,
you should still have some basic common sense.
In a moment,
let's see how badly you eat your words.
Can you all
get out of here?
No.
You stripped this girl bare,
who knows what you're up to?
Sisters,
we'd better keep an eye on this poor unconscious girl.
In case someone uses healing as an excuse
to do something indecent.
This scene feels a bit familiar.
I remember the young lady was the same back then.
Watch if you want to.
Our Master has impeccable medical ethics.
He only thinks about his patients.
He has no twisted thoughts.
I think someone else's twisted thoughts
are pretty obvious, actually.
Her true yang has been severely depleted lately.
Don't read into it.
I'm about to begin.
No one disturb me.
Triple Burner.
Du and Ren meridians.
Purple Palace.
Triple Burner unlocks, channeling earth's veins.
Du and Ren circulate, joining the heavens.
Golden needles ward off doom, mending broken meridians.
Purple Palace restores yang.
Illuminate the empty hall!
Master.
Are you all right?
I'm fine.
Master. Wu Ming.
Master.
Wu Ming!
The Master right now
is the most captivating of all
The vulnerability behind such strength
Sleeping completely defenseless
Chances to be this close to the Master
are truly so rare.
So rare they make my heart ache.
Xiao Tingting
Where are you off to?
To bring medicine to my Master
And take care of him too
Tiring work like delivering medicine
should be left to grown-ups like me.
As for you,
be a good girl and go practice.
If your Master finds out
you haven't been practicing properly lately,
he'll be very disappointed
Since when
did you care about my training?
Of course I do
You're your Master's precious little treasure.
And I,
naturally care for you because of him.
Oh, by the way
Call me "Master's Wife" just once.
And I'll give you a big red envelope
One million!
No way
I'm not calling you "Master's Wife."
And this money,
I don't want it
Little girl
Quite a temper, huh.
Honey
Your loving medicinal meal is here
Who's in there?
If you don't open up,
once I smash this door down,
you're dead.
Guards!
Right now,
break this door down for me
Yes, ma'am
Sister
Why is it you?
I was just taking care of Wu Ming
What,
is there a problem?
Then why didn't you open the door?
And there were
strange noises
You must have heard wrong
Fine
You take over caring for Wu Ming
I'm tired
You two
Stand guard right here
Don't let anyone in
Yes, ma'am
Wait, no
You two,
move further away
Yes, ma'am